Now is the era of Hanwha Life Esports 22
As the sole representative of LCK 22
They are advanced to the First Stand 22
The start of the first group competition 22
was not that great 22
but we all pulled ourselves together
and it feels like we've been rewarded for our efforts
I'm happy and the best teams from each region
are gathering here
In that competition
we strongly want to prove ourselves with great determination
This was the first tournament we played as LCK CUP
and also the first using the Fearless Draft
Through twenty matches,
We improved both as a team and individually
It was a season of learning and growth
Although we faced difficulties early on
we gave each other feedback and set our direction well
During this season
fans' support felt more special
and more meaningful than ever
During this tournament
our performance improved significantly
so I felt both excitement and enjoyment
Now, the First Stand tournament will also follow the Fearless rules
And since we are
the team that won under these rules
we are confident we can perform well
Since it's a tournament held at LoL Park
We will do our best to show our strongest performance
Winning the LCK CUP and representing LCK at the First Stand
And since it is hosted in Korea
we will do our best to achieve great results
and aim for victory
As it is an upcoming international tournament
just like in the LCK CUP
I think I need to prepare diligently
I think I had a great time during the LCK CUP, so
I hope to continue enjoying the upcoming
international matches as well
I sincerely thank the fans
I will continue to work hard
From a viewer's perspective, it may have been exhausting
and there were moments when faith wavered
but thanks to your unwavering support
we have the honor of representing LCK
so we want to meet the fans' expectations
I want to showcase the performance you desire
Just like in the LCK CUP, we will do our best
we will prepare well and aim for victory
I believe we are
the strongest contender for the championship